## **Georgios Oikonomitsios**

oikonomitsios.george@outlook.com | (+974) 6652-5070 | <u>george.oikonomitsios.com</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/georgeoikonomitsios</u> 880 street, zone 26, building 34, Doha, Qatar

### **SUMMARY**

An experienced Director of Services, with more than 10 years demonstrated history of working in the aviation industry. Looking forward to transition to a higher management position or back to the education industry utilizing all knowledge, communication and management skills acquired throughout the years.

### **EXPERIENCE**

QATAR AIRWAYS	DOHA, QATAR
Cabin Services Director	09/2018 - Current
<ul> <li>Responsible for the optimal operation of each flight, ensuring the safety and wellbeing for all</li> </ul>	
<ul> <li>passengers and crew.</li> <li>Responsible for documenting and reporting all flight details, security, and medical incidents with HQ.</li> <li>Promoting a healthy working environment motivating each cabin crew to flourish, grow and continuously improve their performance and service towards our customers.</li> <li>Regularly selected to lead high profile VIP flights for unique events.</li> </ul>	
Cabin Senior	
<ul> <li>Continuously improved the performance and competitiveness of the cabin crew team and the service they provided to our customers through leadership and management of cabin crew.</li> <li>Ranked 2<sup>nd</sup> scoring 98% in the Cabin Senior selection assessment among all eligible candidates.</li> </ul>	09/2015 - 09/2018
<ul> <li>F1 Premium Cabin Crew</li> <li>Provided an outstanding customer service, by creating an environment that impressed our Premium Class customers, through service and by recognizing their individual needs.</li> </ul>	
F2 Economy Cabin Crew	
<ul> <li>Provided a consistent and outstanding customer service to all our customers to increase their loyalty and establish the reputation and image of Cabin Crew as a distinct competitive advantage for Qatar Airways.</li> </ul>	05/2013 - 09/2015
NEW AGE ENGLISH	09/2011 - 05/2013
English Language Teacher	
<ul><li>Worked with children aged 5 to 12 years old, teaching English as a language</li></ul>	
	02/2011 - 07/2011

**EDUCATION** 

# NATIONAL AND KAPODISTRIAN UNIVERSITY OF ATHENS BSc Geology ATHENS, GREECE Expected 2024

Studied the subterranean environment of Greece, geological techniques, and phenomena of earth.

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

•	edX & Harvard University   CS50x - CS50's Introduction to Computer Science	Ongoing
•	Udemy   The Complete 2021 Web Development Bootcamp	Ongoing
•	Udemy   Python GUI Programming Using PyQt5	07/2020
•	Udemy   Linux Administration Bootcamp: Go from Beginner to Advanced	04/2020
•	Udemy   Python GUI Programming Using Tkinter and SQLite3	02/2020
•	Qatar Airways   Senior Leadership Excellence	08/2018
•	Qatar Airways   Cultural and Emotional Intelligence	11/2017
•	Pan-Hellenic Seminar on Children with Learning Difficulties	05/2011
CVILLE		

#### **SKILLS**

Operating Systems: Windows, Mac OS X, Linux

Office: Office 365, Outlook, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, SharePoint

**Communication Platforms:** Zoom, Microsoft Teams, Google Hangouts, Slack **Programming Languages:** Python, Unity, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, jQuery, SQL

### **LANGUAGES**

Greek – Proficient; English – Proficient (Proficiency, Cambridge University); German – Intermediate (Grundstufe, Goethe Institute)